{
  "questions": [
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "question": "Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",
      "answer": "<script>",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "<java>",
        "<javascript>",
        "<head>"]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "question": "In Java, which of those allows duplicate elements?",
      "answer": "List",
      "incorrect_answers": [ 
      "Set",
      "None of the above",
      "All of the above"
     ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mutiple",
      "question": "Which of the following is not a language that has been taught in this course?",
      "answer": "Python"
      "incorrect_answers": [ 
      "JavaScript",
      "CSS",
      "HTML"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "fill_in",
      "question": "What does JDK stand for",
      "answer":"Java Development Kit",
      "incorrect_answers": [
     ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "question": "CSS stands for",
      "answer":"Cascading Style Sheets",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cool Style Sheets",
        "Coding Style Sheets",
        "Colorful Style Sheets"
     ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "question": "Where are JS files and CS files references",
      "answer":"<head>",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "<title>",
        "<h1>"
        "<body>"
     ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "question": "Which of the following is not an access modifier?",
      "answer":"All of the above",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Private",
        "Public",
        "Protected"
     ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "question": "How do you change the background color?",
      "answer":"back-ground color",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "color",
        "background",
        "All of the above"
     ]
    },
    {
      "type": "fill_in",
      "question": "What does the following statement print? System.out.print( 5 + "5") ",
      "answer":" 5 5 ",
      "incorrect_answers": [
     ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "question": "What signifies a new paragraph?",
      "answer":"<p>",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "<paragraph>",
        "<para>",
        "<br>"
     ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "question": "There is only one way to declare a function in Javascript",
      "answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
     ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "question": "A variable can be changed when the final keyword is used",
      "answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers": [ 
        "True"
     ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "question": "to declare a non-static method, the keyword non-static must be used ",
      "answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
     ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "question": "In Java, = and == will produce the same result",
      "answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers": [ 
        "True"
     ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "question": "Java and Javascript are the same.",
      "answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
     ]
    },
   {
      "type": "boolean",
      "question": "<hr> produces a visible horizontal line",
      "answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
     ]
    },
   {
      "type": "boolean",
      "question": "<br> produces a single line break",
      "answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
     ]
    },
   {
      "type": "boolean",
      "question": "Danger and Red will produce the same color",
      "answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
     ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "question": "Text - color is used to change font color",
      "answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"    
     ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "question": "A separate file is needed for CSS and JavaScript",
      "answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers": [ "True"
     ]
    },
    { 
      "type": "fill_in",
      "question": "px stands for:",
      "answer": "Pixels",
      "incorrect_answers": [
       ]
    },
    {
     "type": "fill_in",
     "question": "API stands for",
     "answer": "Application Programming Interface",
     "incorrect_answers":[
    ]
    }

]}
